Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
What is the meaning
of this intrusion?
Heil Hitler.
-Heil Hitler.
Obergruppenfuhreh Weiss.
thank you for joining us.
What is the purpose
of your visit. sir?
Trust me when I say
I did not wish to
come here today.
but our enemies
have grown stronger
and the Fuhrer demands results.
We are to go to live
testing immediately.
But Herr Hoffman.
we simply are not ready.
Dr. Mengel has not approved
the latest calculations.
I agree sir.
We are still weeks away.
I cannot...
-Silence!
Obergruppenfuhreh.
do you want to stand the risk
of what the Fuhrer is asking?
I do.
But I further
regret to inform you
that the allied forces
are uncomfortably close!
The time is now!
And it would seem that we may
have a rat
among us
because our enemy
has learned about what we're
trying to achieve here.
And if Germany
is to stand any
chance whatsoever
of winning this war.
we must act now.
So Fuhrer considers this
Germany's top priority
and he's making his way
to this location
as we speak.
We must be ready.
Obergruppenfuhreh.
that is the most terrible news.
But I beg you.
we simply cannot.
Enough. enough.
Well.
if the Fuhrer commands it.
then of course we will obey.
Hmm?
Move to human trials
immediately.
So be it.
God protect us.
Go. go.
Please.
Obergruppenfuhreh.
please.
feel free to make
yourself comfortable.
We'll be ready to
test later today.
Tell me.
when can we expect the Fuhrer?
I do not have safety test.
I was instructed to
oversea the initial tests
and report back.
It was made clear.
We wait for no one.
not even the Fuhrer.
Very well. sir.
Very well. indeed.
Are you crazy. boy?
You're really going
to smoke that here?
It might be my last one.
Use your brain. you domkoft.
This is madness.
We are not ready.
-Sir.
Focus. please.
For Germany.
Gentlemen.
you may be cowardly dogs
charged with desertion. but
listen to me when I say
this is your redemption.
The whole war has been a tragedy
and the German people have
become feared by the world
for they think that we
are monsters.
Today.
you will show them
the power of our might
and turn their
fears into reality.
If this experiment works.
you will become soldiers
beyond men
For your strength
and fearlessness
will be unmatched.
Take a moment
and think of your family.
Think how proud
you will make them.
the Fuhrer will be
to unleash you
upon his enemies.
Yeah?
This is for the father dead.
Heil Hitler!
Gentlemen.
we are ready to execute.
The Fuhrer will be joining us.
What is your command?
We wait for no man.
Remember?
Start the detonation
sequence immediately.
Dr. Fisher.
please starts the
detonation sequence.
Dr. Muller.
I honestly believe that the
blast radius calculations
have not been verified.
We must take
further precautions.
Tell me who is the informant.
You're only going to make
it worse for yourself.
You won't get any
information out of me. Jerry.
Alpha Meyer.
there's an urgent phone
call for you. sir.
From Obergruppenfuhreh
Dietrich himself.
I'm not done with you.
I look forward to it.
Nazi saluting swine.
Saved by the bell.
Come on. you bastard.
Come on.
That's the ticket.
Quiet.
Come on.
Why do they never go quietly?
Right.
You won't been needing this.
and that is how I'm sat in
front of you this morning. sir.
Bloody hell.
Sounds like you've been
through it. haven't you.
Clever escape.
Sounds like lady luck
was on your side too.
Ah.
-Hmm.
Yes. well. I did think
I was a goner sir.
Truth be told.
But.
luckily I was
interrupted by Dietrich.
whoever that is.
I owe the chap some thanks.
Ah.
Hold that thought.
That is one of the reasons
I wanted to see you
today. Craftman.
Our allied efforts have been
somewhat successful.
We're slowly choking the
enemy here in France.
But that will all be in
vain if we don't act now.
One of our undercovers
has fed us information
about the German effort
to create super soldiers
in some overrun French bunker.
Super soldier. sir?
I'm getting to that.
You see.
we embedded one of our own
as a low level
officer in that bunker
going by the pseudonym.
Heinrich Hans.
His orders
were to report about
German activity in the area
every 48 hours.
And yesterday.
he failed to report back.
It's the first time Hans has
missed an information drop.
We're awfully
worried about the lad
and there are rumors that Hitler
was supposed to be
at the bunker. but
hasn't been
confirmed by our man.
I see. sir.
That's really not good. sir.
No lad.
it's not.
We are concerned that
Hans has been compromised.
God help him if he's
been discovered.
Indeed sir.
The Germans are ruthless
at extracting information.
Exactly.
But then again.
we received a telegram
late last night
from another one of our
men behind enemy lines.
He stated that he had
intercepted a high level
German communication
between that bunker and your
crazy Jerry friend.
Obergruppenfitch.
whatever his bloody name is.
Dietrich.
By God. you mean the very same?
Yes.
The very same man
you claim saved your
life last night.
It appears he was busy till
the early hours of the morning.
The report states
that Ditchy. your friend.
made several inquiries about
the German information network
and it would seem
that they've lost
communication with that bunker.
Reports of an
explosion of sorts.
I see.
So our man Hans could
be dead already.
Equally. there's a chance he
could be hiding undercover.
A chance.
Yes.
A chance indeed.
And I. and are allied forces.
and Winston himself.
God preserve him.
all agree that the intel
that Hans possesses
is essential to our success.
If he is alive.
he needs to be extracted
immediately.
Ah. I see where
this is going sir.
I should bloody well hope so.
You are the best man we have
and we need you
back in the field.
You are the only man
this side of the channel
who's actually qualified to lead
both American and
British troops.
And William J. Donovan of
the American OSS would agree.
So what's the plan sir?
Good man.
Look at this.
We need a scouting team to go
here.
Now set up a perimeter
and establish all
German activity
going in and coming
out of that bunker.
Report your findings.
Hmm.
Sounds straightforward sir.
Hmm?
This is where you need
to use your discretion.
If the location is tame.
and you feel you can
infiltrate that facility.
proceed into the bunker
and see if you can
locate any information on Hans.
Then extract him.
And any information you
have on what the bloody hell
those Jerrys are doing.
it'd be quite useful.
Well I'll be needing a team sir.
Ah.
way ahead of you. Craftman.
Handpicked by me.
A Brit.
three yanks.
and a medic in case you
encounter any nasties out there.
Now your team is
waiting for you.
It's a bit of a drive
so I need you
to leave
now.
Alright sir.
Could you just
talk with me about
what you meant by
super soldiers sir?
Ah. bloody hell.
Yes.
Sit.
The objective seems
straightforward enough.
But this feel like a suicide
mission to anyone else?
And why's only six of us?
It feels a little
light if you asked me.
It feels like you're
scared to me. buddy.
Fuck off. Johnson.
I ain't scared of shit.
I'm just seeing five
dudes and a woman.
Come on. man.
Excuse me. Russo.
I'm not just some woman.
My job is to keep
you bastards alive.
Hey don't you gold me mixing
me up with these two misfits.
My mama raised a gentleman.
Oh. bastards are we?
That's the thanks we get
for saving your asses.
You Yanks just turned
up to this party.
Oh. let's just admit
the truth here.
Y'all were getting your butts
whooped 'til we arrived.
Fuck you.
Oh. wasn't it only last year
that you guys been saved
by your own civilians
in those little boats. right?
That is what makes us
Brits so resilient.
Dunkirk had us up against the
ropes but we bounced back.
Oh shit.
He speaks.
-And about time too.
We got some questions. sir.
Sorry gents.
and miss.
you wouldn't believe the
last 24 hours I've had.
I was just catching up.
Understandable sir. but
do you mind if we discuss
what the hell we're
walking into here?
Yeah. we're gonna do this
with just a six of us. sir?
Right. well that's us.
We're on foot from here.
Chop chop.
Getting close now.
Best set of base camp soon.
Ready when you are sir.
The coordinates put
the bunker up ahead.
Well.
looks dead to me.
It's a ghost town.
Alright.
phase two of the plant.
Infiltrate the bunker.
Let's get some grub in us
and wait for the
cover of darkness.
I missed what she said.
What she saying?
I'm sorry I wasn't listening.
I was just distracted
by your eyes. Miss.
This man has three wives.
You wanna be number four?
What?
Russo?
Johnson?
You take the lead.
West. you're with me.
Plumb.
Ms. Hayman.
you take the rear.
Right. so send in the
expendable chosen first.
Speak for yourself.
I ain't expendable.
Gentlemen. I'm just
trying to give us
the best fighting chance.
Of course. of course.
Ain't nothing getting
past us. aye Russo?
Yeah. fair point.
Big guns.
Got it.
After we get in there.
we sweep out the
place for any Jerrys.
Then we head to the comms room.
Alan. see if you can
get it up and running.
Copy that.
For now. that's
all the information
I have to give you lads.
Well let's kill these
German bastards.
Not so fast. Russo.
We have a man in there
pretending to be one of theirs.
The last thing I need is you
blowing his bloody brains out.
So what the hell you want
us to go down there for?
If Nazis are waiting for us.
it's not like they're gonna
give us hugs and kisses. right?
I'm just saying. lad.
think before you shoot.
Alan.
I know you are a comms man.
but you mind need to fall back
on your basic training here.
And what about me?
Do I get a gun?
Several rounds.
Semi-automatic.
You got that sweetheart?
Got it.
sweetheart.
Good luck miss.
Well they definitely
lost power...
Shh.
Keep your bloody
voice down. Plumb.
Hey. hey.
I want to get the
chomp on these guys.
Not the other way around.
Sorry.
Real sorry.
Anything?
Negative sir.
Well I don't like this much.
What?
How is this not the
best case scenario?
If there's no one here.
there's no one here to shoot.
no one to shoot back at us.
I was looking forward to
taking out some Nazi scum.
Me too.
You're both animals.
and I agree with Ms. Hayman.
Robert.
God. it's so quiet.
All right team.
let's focus up and
concentrate on finding
the comms room.
I don't know about that sir.
I think we should
do a full sweep
before we get too comfortable.
I hate to admit it sir.
but I agree with
Russo on this one.
Can I make a suggestion. sir?
I'm all ears. Johnson.
I think we can safely assume
that this area is dead.
So West. Plumb and the doc
continue to search
for the comms room.
We can check down here.
It's up to you if you go with
them or you come with us.
It's not a bad shout. Johnson.
Alright. let's split up.
West.
-Sir.
You go upstairs with these two.
Plumb. Hayman.
if West says jump. you jump.
Got it sir.
You can't be serious.
Splitting up is like the worst
possible thing we could do.
Plumb.
if you want to ask a
question. I'll listen.
But if you ever
challenge me again.
I will have you
shot against a post.
I'm sorry. sir.
It won't happen again.
Make sure that it doesn't.
No. no. I mean it sir.
I apologize.
West?
Sir.
Fall out.
Keep up. Plumb.
Let's get on it.
I am not convinced
that we're gonna find
what we're looking for
and even if we do
find a comms room.
there ain't gonna be no
electricity to power it.
We were told to find the room.
Let's just find the
damn room. okay.
Plumb does have a point though.
We've been split up
and sent on a pointless quest.
Nothing.
Nada.
Looks like a generator room.
Wait here.
Quest.
you make it sound like a game.
We were told to find the comms
and that's what we're doing.
If it's inoperable.
then we'll go find the others.
But not before we've
located it and assessed it.
Okay?
Perhaps they evacuated.
Looks like the main
generator's down.
At least the backup
is still working.
I got a bad feeling about this.
You and me both.
Well on you. old boy.
They must have
located the power.
Let's go.
Stop.
Both of you.
What the hell was that?
Did anybody see that?
What?
Why was it?
Sir. did you see it?
I didn't see anything
but I certainly heard something.
I don't think we should
go down there sir.
Get it
together. soldier.
I'm ready to take
these fuckers out. sir.
All right. go.
The comms room has got
to be on this level
because if you go any deeper.
you wouldn't get a signal.
Copy that.
West.
It's here.
Your move. Russo.
Shh.
Shhh.
Ma'am?
Ma'am.
it is okay.
No.
Back.
Well Plumb?
I think we may just be in luck.
Thank God.
What's next?
Well I'm gonna send out a signal
and see if I get anything back.
No closer.
Father.
Who will hear us?
I'm gonna find the others.
Nothing I can do here.
Well I should come.
No. no. no. you're not
gonna both leave me here.
Miss Hayman is not
going anywhere.
Miss.
where are the others?
Out.
Need to get out.
They are coming.
Out.
You ain't going
anywhere. little miss.
Please.
out.
They are coming.
The fuck is she
talking about. Russo?
Nazis down here.
Freeze!
Whoa. whoa. it's me.
It's West for fuck sake.
Jesus Christ. man.
Where are the rest of you?
We found the comms.
Guess this place
isn't abandoned.
This is the only
one we found so far.
West. secure this woman.
See if you can get some
information out of her.
It is West. man.
Thank God.
You could have
knocked on something.
You're scared us half to death.
We have a developing
situation here.
Come on.
Gimme your arms.
Is that entirely necessary?
Until we know more.
it's absolutely necessary.
Plumb. how's the comms?
We have power.
I'm just trying to
establish a connection
and not be discovered.
We're going to die.
You need to leave here.
What is she talking about?
It's all
she's been saying.
We need to get more
information out of her.
What?
She's burning up.
We need to get her stable
before we can get anything
useful out of her.
Excuse me. miss.
do you have a name?
Out.
Need to get out.
What do
you think it is?
I don't know.
Sounds injured.
On you. Russo.
The roses need watering.
I repeat the roses
need watering.
Over.
We are going to die.
We need to leave it here.
Why?
What's down there?
Monsters.
Miss?
The
watering can is full.
The watering can is full.
We are in the bunker. over.
Who goes there?
What do you see. Russo?
Don't shoot.
It's me.
Hans.
That's him.
Got our guy.
What the fuck is that?
Don't just stand
there. get after him.
Bollocks!
They must have found Jerry.
Plumb. tell 'em we've been
encountered the enemy.
No. no. no. you're
not leaving us.
Boss said if we hear
gun fire to join him.
Go!
What the fuck is that?
Come on. let them know.
Plumb. snap out of it.
We are under enemy fire.
I repeat. we are
under enemy fire.
What the hell
causes something like this?
His skin. it's all melted.
You know what boss.
we found Hans.
Most of him anyway.
I say that's mission
accomplished.
I vote we get the
fuck out of here.
Crass. Johnson. but
I agree with you.
We found our man.
time to report back to HQ.
Sir.
you better take a look at this.
Come out with your hands clear.
Schnell.
Come out now.
Ah. fuck it.
Well. according to this.
the Nazis were developing
some sort of explosive device
that alters one's DNA
when exposed to it.
That's some devil kinda shit.
Mm.
it would seam
that the Fuhrer himself
signed off on it.
You're saying Adolf
Hitler is here?
I'm saying it's a
distinct possibility.
Jesus.
Wait. you think there's
more of them down here?
If I were a betting man.
I'd say that explosion
is what caused that poor
bastard's situation.
So yes. you think there's
more of them down here?
Unfortunately Johnson.
I would say that is a safe bet.
Fuck.
I'm with Johnson.
Hans is dead.
I say.
we get the fuck out of here.
Oh. I don't like sound
of that gentleman.
Shit.
Sir?
Agreed. time to go.
Sounds like they're everywhere.
Sounds like
there's a lot of 'em.
Be that as it may.
we have to get out of
here and find the others.
Sir.
Aim for the heads.
We are in need of assistance.
Can anyone read me?
Come in.
We are in need of assistance.
Over.
What do you think is
going on out there?
I can't imagine.
but this place clearly
isn't abandoned
and we need to get
out of here alive.
Oh God.
I'm gonna die in here.
We are gonna die in here.
This is where I'm
gonna meet my death.
Get it together. Plumb.
Now I suggest that
you communicate
we need an extraction plan.
Yesterday. Plumb.
We are in need of
immediate extraction over.
We gotta get outta here. sir.
Back up.
Back up now.
Move. move.
Thank you.
What the fuck are they?
We found information
suggesting the Nazis
were using this facility
for some sort of bio weapon.
And they turned
themselves into this?
By the way. sir.
I owe you a pint.
And you owe me a beer.
Have you ever encountered
anything like this before. sir?
I for damn sure haven't.
Come on. let's go.
There's more coming.
Move.
The fuck.
Oh. she's dead.
Come in.
We are in need of
extraction. over.
This is hopeless.
How's she doing?
She's getting
worse by the minute
and it's all because
of this nasty bugger.
It looks like
something's bit her.
You think an animal did that?
Well. that's the thing. Plumb.
It looks human to me.
Wait.
you think a human did that
and that's what's
making her sick?
Whoever bit her
was already sick.
Come in.
communication received. over.
Oh. thank you kindly.
How many units are you sending
and are they en route?
One truck.
extraction point
same as drop off.
three hours out.
Going radio dark.
Over
Radio dark?
No. no. no. no. no.
You don't understand.
We need extraction now.
It's not looking good. is it?
We're gonna have to haul
ourselves two miles.
That's only if we
can get out of here.
Oh. now why do you go
and say things like that?
I'm already feeling
down on my luck
and now you go and destroy any
last bit of hope that I have.
Oh Christ. you gave us a fright.
Are you feeling all right?
Do you understand me?
Ma'am. are you
feeling all right?
Plumb.
help me sit her down.
Is that really necessary?
Did you see what I just saw?
The poor woman was
having a seizure?
No. no. there was
something in her eyes.
All right. if you're
going to restrain her.
at least help me
make her comfortable.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Johnson.
I know he was your mate.
I also know what it's
like to lose a soldier.
Johnson.
we need you.
We need you here with us.
All right?
Well.
we had our objectives.
There's nothing we
can do for Hans now.
Let's hope Alan
solved our problem
in the communications office.
We can get out of here
with no more casualties.
All right. sounds
like a plan. sir.
What do you say soldier?
Let's give 'em hell. sir.
That's what I like to hear.
West?
Aye?
What do you reckon?
Coast is clear?
Cannot hear a thing. sir.
Aye
On you.
Miss?
That sounds like the others.
Quietly now.
I
I wanna die.
Quietly.
Go. go. go. go. go. go.
West. knife.
Distraction.
Johnson.
Come on then. you wankers.
Nice one. lads.
Right.
we've made enough noise.
we should probably
get out of here.
West. lead the way.
What in God's name?
I'm sure you did
everything you could. Pat.
It just all happened so fast.
She did this to Plumb?
She fell unconscious
as. as Plumb was getting
somewhere with comms.
And then she had some
sort of seizure and
Plumb thought it'd be a
good idea to restrain her.
Seems y'all did a great
job of restraining her.
Sorry. miss.
You have no idea.
She was so strong
and she escaped her
binds in seconds.
And then poor Plumb
was trying to.
he was trying to protect
me. but she was just.
she was just too strong.
Hayman.
calm down.
I understand you've
been through an ordeal.
but we don't know how
many more of these things
are out there.
Zombies.
Nazi fucking zombies.
You've been to too
many picture shows.
Zombies.
Well. whatever these things are.
we discovered
when we were looking
for our man. Hans.
that he was.
How. did you find him?
We discovered that this place
was being used to test and
develop biological weapons.
When one is exposed
to the blast.
their biology changes
and they revert back
to their absolute
basic human instinct.
The urge to eat.
What exactly
did you see down there?
All right. we've got company.
How many of them. West?
One.
two.
five I can see.
Maybe more.
Let's be smart about this. lads.
If we're quiet.
they may just pass.
All right.
and just know if
this goes wrong.
we're fighting 'em in here.
Worth the risk. I'd say.
Plumb did
request an extraction.
And?
And they're sending a truck
to collect us at
the drop off point.
0600 hours.
Plenty of time. right sir?
Sir?
Okay.
Well in hindsight.
we have a slightly bigger issue.
Sir?
Containment.
Well?
Whatever those things are.
The zombies.
Whatever you want to call them.
they can't get out of here.
But sir. our mission.
Our mission was one thing.
from what we've witnessed here.
every single person here
has been compromised.
You have
the ones with the melting skin.
and then you have these
who look like us.
but act like them.
Her bite mark.
So those who are
primarily infected
can infect others
through saliva.
My God. they are zombies.
-Zombies.
And we can't let that
get out into the world.
Not that I disagree
with you. sir. but
playing devil's advocate here.
We arrived hours after
the original explosion.
There could be a few of
them already out there.
Just a feeling.
A feeling?
Well. that and common sense.
From the amount we've
encountered here.
it only makes sense
that they retreated to
their natural environment.
which is to say to
hide in darkness.
And we.
my friends.
are going to trap
them down here.
Sending us all to
an early grave.
Look. I don't like it
anymore than you do. alright?
But we have an obligation here
that transcends this bloody war.
an obligation to humanity.
How many
days.
weeks.
months
before those
fucking things.
Zombies.
Okay sir.
what's the plan?
Well.
for starters.
we have less than two hours.
So.
how much ammunition
have you all got?
Had to.
Sorry.
Okay.
so do we need to
go over it again?
No. we've got this. sir.
Shoot them in the head.
Keep a bullet for yourself.
Get bitten. it's over.
All for one and
all that bullshit.
Okay.
West. you stay with Hayman.
give her a ten second head start
and then start shooting.
Someone needs to get back
to our boys back home
and let them know
what's going on here.
No sir.
Can't we all leave together?
I wish we could.
but the situation is far
graver than we anticipated.
Johnson.
you ready?
Shit.
Hell no.
Soldier?
I'm joking. boss.
Let's kill those
Nazi zombie fucks.
That's more like it.
Wish us luck.
Oh. and Miss Hayman.
we get outta this alive.
I sure would love
to take you dancing.
Focus Johnson.
Don't do anything
heroically stupid now.
Well. this is it.
And I'm okay with that.
Well. I'm bloody not.
We're getting out of here.
Shh.
You hear that?
On you. Johnson.
That's all of 'em. sir.
Johnson!
Eat
lead. motherfucker.
Johnson.
Fall back.
Do you think they're safe?
We'll know shortly.
Just a few more. aye Johnson.
Whatever you say. boss.
Come on. you bastards.
Hold it. they're coming.
She's jammed.
The coast is clear.
Hayman. get your.
Hayman. look out!
Good work. Johnson.
Oh shit.
Come on.
Come on. pull back.
I can't get a clear shot.
Hayman!
Oh. fuck it.
Come on. grab your gun.
We're getting the
hell out of here.
Fuck.
No.
You've only got one left.
Get out of here now.
I'll be right behind you.
-You best be.
-Go!
Come here.
Come on your Nazi bastard.
Come on.
You ugly piece of shit.
Keep moving.
Come on.
Sir. my leg.
He's coming.
Come on.
Okay. come on now.
Come on. man.
Come on. Johnson.
Almost there.
Come on. you motherfucker.
Come on.
Piece of
filth.
You motherfucker.
Come on.
West.
West!
Do you think they'll
make it out of there?
I hope so. but
I wouldn't bet on it.
If I had any more ammo.
I'd go back in there. but
this is just a glorified club.
Well. you did what you had to.
We'll see our orders through.
That's
40.
45 minutes till our ride
gets to the extraction point.
Let's go in and help them.
Stay close.
Damn.
Am I glad to see you two.
Let's get the
hell out of here. boss.
-Aye.
-I still owe you that pint.
Help me out. would you?
Come on.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Do you realize
what you just did?
You just ended World War II.
Good
evening. ladies and gentlemen.
This is your trusted
voice. Sherman Wilkins.
bringing you a special report
on the extraordinary alliance
between Britain and America
that has secured
victory over Germany
and its axis of evil.
Germany is defeated.
Hitler's reign is over.
Tonight we celebrate not
just a military triumph.
but the unity and determination
of two great nations
that stood shoulder to
shoulder against tyranny.
enduring the blitz.
the Battle of Normandy.
and countless other trials
with unwavering resolve.
Under the stalwart leadership
of Prime Minister
Winston Churchill
and President
Franklin D. Roosevelt.
the combined forces
of Britain and America
launched a relentless campaign
against the forces of darkness.
Our soldiers fought bravely
on land. sea. and air.
driven by the belief in a
future free from oppression.
Yet amidst the horrors
of conventional warfare.
a sinister and
shocking tale emerged
from the heart of
the enemy's domain.
In their desperate
bid for supremacy.
the German war machine
embarked on grotesque
biological experiments
seeking to create
invincible super soldiers.
These scientists.
blinded by ambition
and devoid of humanity.
tampered with the
very essence of life.
But in their quest for
an unassailable army.
they unwittingly unleashed a
horror beyond their control.
The experiments intended
to bolstered their ranks.
instead gave rise to
nightmare Nazi zombies.
undead soldiers driven by a
mindless hunger for destruction.
These abominations once meant
to turn the tide of war.
instead brought
chaos and devastation
to the third Reich.
In the face of this
unforeseen horror.
it was the joint efforts
of a select few allied soldiers
who stood to face
the Nazi zombies
fighting valiantly to
contain the contagion.
The bravery and sacrifice
of these men and women
was extraordinary as
they confronted an enemy.
unlike any seen before.
Their heroism in the shadows
of war. often unrecognized.
was instrumental in
our ultimate victory.
Hitler is dead.
So here today. we
recognize these individuals
and their valiant efforts.
Tonight as we revel in
this moment of triumph.
we honor the courage. unity.
and sacrifice that carried
us through the darkest days.
Now we must turn our
undivided attention
towards the far east.
If Hitler dead.
will Japan surrender
or will they follow
in Germany's footsteps
and resort to the same
biological experiments
on their armies?
This ladies and
gentlemen is something
that our nations cannot risk.
Winston Churchill
himself has confirmed
that the Americans have a plan
which will be revealed
to us in the coming days.
An act of war to end all wars.
we are asked to remain
steadfast and patient
and victory will be ours.
This is Sherman Wilkins
reminding you that even in
the face of the unimaginable.
the spirit of humanity endures.
Through unity and determination.
we have overcome the
greatest of evils
and we can all sleep
peacefully tonight.
And on that thought.
I bet you all a good night
and God bless.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-